[Simple yet elegant attire,]
[delicate fingers,]
[not a laborer.]
[Young but composed,]
[either a young master or a swindler.]
Young master, do you know me?
Coincidentally, just met.
That's your "recruiting a son-in-law" notice, right?
Are you willing to marry into my family?
Yes.
How much bride price do you want?
Nothing.
You can bring your own.
Any conditions?
Get married within ten days.
[What a liar.]
Oh, that's too bad.
My parents
are on a mission.
They won't be back for a month.
It seems you'll have to
look elsewhere for a match.
Farewell.
Ah,
if your parents knew you were using them
as an excuse to avoid marriage,
they'd surely
be pleased.
That's avoiding disaster, okay?
If they're watching from above,
they wouldn't want me to be tricked.
Besides, how can a perfect guy fall from the sky?
Forget it.
I'll go to the Matchmaker Pavilion.
Let's go.
Is it always this hard
to marry into a family with my own dowry?
You finally came.
You are?
I run the Matchmaker Pavilion.
I've been waiting for you.
Come in.
Su Yuejiao,
an escort from Su's Escort Agency,
is looking for a husband.
She is young
but has a strong desire to get married.
The reason is unknown.
Because of her identity and rumors,
she is suspected of
domestic violence.
Currently, no one in Yunjing City
is interested in her.
I feel offended.
Miss,
would you like to say it again?
I value efficiency.
The right medicine can work wonders.
Just tell me what you need.
Oh, right.
Recruiting a son-in-law is more expensive than getting married.
If you accept, just come.
The best age is about my age,
no more than 30 years old.
Do you accept children?
Single or widower without children.
It's better to know some kong fu.
No serious disability.
I'll take over the Escort Agency in the future.
If he knows how to manage a family,
he may be helpful.
He should be literate.
It's better to get married within a month.
Why a month?
Is someone in your family ill?
Or...
No, no, no.
Nothing like that.
I just want to get things settled quickly.
Are you open to blind dates?
Blind dates?
Yunjing City is so lively,
much more than Ning'an County.
I don't know when I'll be here next.
Don't be so pessimistic.
In half a month,
we'll be living in this city.
Master wouldn't let you move here.
He didn't agree this time either,
but I'm here anyway.
So,
do you like this city?
Yeah.
Do you want to stay here?
That's good.
After I win the Nebula Assembly
and become famous in the Yun State,
I'll show you around here.
Okay.
Let's go shopping.
Come on.
Yicheng, hurry up.
Here you are.
Sugar-coated haws.
I want one.
Thanks.
See?
Clothes
make the man.
I look presentable now, right?
Young Master, you should go back.
Oh, right.
It's about time.
Prepare a carriage.
Go back to Ning'an?
No,
to the Matchmaker Pavilion.
I'm off.
Welcome, Mr. Fu.
Excuse me,
is the young lady here?
You come here every day.
Your persistence
will pay off.
She's here today.
Oh.
Tang Xin, is this what people wear?
It's so uncomfortable.
I can't even throw a punch in it.
Hey.
I like it.
What do you like?
This is the wedding invitation.
Pick any lucky day
on it.
You look strong.
I think you can have five sons.
I've already picked out names for them,
they're all on this piece of paper.
Hey, I barely said anything,
and you've already decided on the number of sons.
With his physique,
he can easily have ten.
Miss, Fu Xiang from the Fuyun Escort Agency wishes to see you.
Isn't he my father's errand boy?
What does he want with me?
I don't know.
Shopkeeper Li said he came here for you several times.
I don't want to see him.
Yes.
Wait.
Let him in.
OK.
What can I do for you?
Miss Zhang,
over the years,
our Fuyun Escort Agency has been serving the Grand Tutor,
without a hitch.
We've always wanted
to help with your business.
That would be great.
Miss,
just rest assured,
as long as it's your request,
we'll treat it as our top priority.
Get to the point.
Nebula Assembly.
Can Fuyun Escort Agency
take charge of the Nebula Assembly?
It's just a gathering of literati.
No need for guards.
I may be rough,
but I understand
this is the Grand Tutor's idea.
I just wanna repay you
for your years of support,
and meet some influential people
to boost business.
You're so smart.
I see.
So...
Well...
You can think about my suggestion.
If you need,
Fuyun Agency will do anything for you.
Mr. Fu,
please.
Don't bother to see me off.
Humph.
What a jerk.
You don't need to escort goods anymore.
You should take care of me and educate the children.
Don't ask.
I'll support you.
I'm also going to take three concubines.
And you should respect my parents.
Well.
Three is too few.
A hero like you
should have at least ten.
Yeah.
If you have a suitable one,
you can introduce her to me.
This man is really straightforward
and frank.
But the information from the Matchmaker Pavilion
is totally different.
You saw through me so quickly.
See?
Yeah, my wife
is the only one who knows the real me.
Ouch!
You offended it.
Sir,
how can I get to Su's Escort Agency?
You're an escort?
This road,
go straight to the end.
Thank you.
Now it doesn't listen to me.
What are you waiting for?
Teach her a lesson!
You are the kind of person
who should be left to your wives.
If you want to be related to me,
no way.
Come on!
Why are you again?
You want to be a hero to save a beauty.
Pretending to meet by chance.
We must be fated to meet.
I was just about to look for you.
I'm just an escort,
not much money to scam.
Find someone else.
Scam money?
I think there must be some misunderstanding.
I didn't expect you to be so bad-tempered,
and not behave as a woman should.
You flirt with this pretty boy.
Teach her a lesson!
What are you talking about?
You've read the post, so you're mine.
This is Yunjing City.
Don't be so rude.
My family arranged this.
We just met.
First time.
I don't like her.
What do you think?
Wow, this guy is marrying Su Yuejiao.
That's like saving her from a burning building.
Who in Yunjing City would want her?
Bro,
you're a living saint.
Did you hear that? Marrying you is your lucky day.
Fu Xiang, you big man, always so sarcastic.
Got the guts to fight me?
Hey, I'm in a bad mood today.
I'll teach you a lesson for my bro.
Let you know what a real man is.
Marriage
should be based on mutual consent.
How can you force someone to marry you?
Who are you? It's none of your business.
So rude.
Yun State is a country of etiquette.
It's everyone's responsibility to follow the rules.
This guy is really rude.
How dare you meddle with such a small body.
I'll shut you up first.
Beat him.
Brother
Do you think the boss wants to get married or not?
Anyway, no one is worthy of my sister.
Something happened.
Brother.
Faca.
The boss is fighting with someone.
Where?
Who is she fighting with?
Fu Xiang and his men.
What happened up front?
Miss, it's Fu Xiang.
And someone else
started a fight with Su Yuejiao.
Su Yuejiao?
From Su's Escort Agency?
That's right.
She was just matchmaking upstairs.
She flew down.
Quick, drive them away.
They're blocking the way.
No need.
If anything's damaged inside,
make sure someone pays for it.
Yes, Miss.
Take the back carriage.
Su Yuejiao, you're indeed fierce.
No one will want you.
I think you'll never get married.
I think your life will end today.
You're quite bold, aren't you?
I didn't expect you to be good at talking
but not at martial arts.
You men bully a girl.
That's the best of the people in Yunjing City.
Yeah.
How can these men
bully her?
Isn't that the young lady of the Su Family?
How can she do that?
Maybe they were beaten by the girl.
You shut up.
You pretty boy.
I'll teach you a lesson today.
You big guy only pick on the weak.
You have no guts. Come and fight me.
Hey.
I can see that
this girl is bullying you guys.
I just saw the official carriage passing by.
I'll report it to the government for you.
I can't go to the government again.
I'll be killed by my father.
Let's go.
This gentleman
must be an escort, too.
You look extraordinary.
You are different from those guys.
Are you afraid?
I'm not afraid of you.
You flatter others.
Don't you know your own ability?
Su Yuejiao,
do you want to stay in Yunjing?
I'll beat you.
Come on.
Move aside.
My Lord.
My Lord, are you okay?
Fu Xiang, what did you do?
Sister, take a break.
I'll beat him for you.
Move aside.
Just let him go like this?
What happened to your bullying?
I didn't expect that Fuyun Agency
would run away from a fight.
Isn't that the escort's habit?
We Su's Agency is not like that.
What did you do
to my sister?
Brother.
Nothing.
This young master just stood up for me.
You may not be skilled in martial arts,
but you're quite honorable.
Thanks.
Just doing my part.
As a token of gratitude,
I'll share a secret with you.
If you're serious about marriage,
avoid the Matchmaker Pavilion.
Farewell.
Hmm.
I feel better now.
You were on a blind date, right?
Why did you fight?
Don't mention it.
The Matchmaker Pavilion sent me such a guy.
He was said to be well-educated
and handsome.
He's just a rude ruffian.
No way.
It's said that the Matchmaker Pavilion is very effective.
And Fu Xiang
came to challenge me for no reason.
I'll beat him up in the arena.
In the whole Yunjing,
only your escort agency can compete with him.
He's been giving you trouble for a long time.
But it was that swindler,
no,
that young master,
who was obviously weak,
but stood up for me.
Though both are men,
they are not the same.
Is it the handsome young master?
Yes.
The one who brought betrothal gifts to marry into your family?
Then why don't you just marry him?
Yeah.
I can't deal with you.
Who is that young master?
I don't know.
What's his name?
Do you know who you are?
I'm Su Yuejiao.
Forget it.
It means we are not meant to be.
I should go to the Matchmaker Pavilion.
It doesn't work. Why do you go there?
I have to make this swindler
close the shop.
That's called closing the business.
Wow.
People from Yunjing
get married in ten days,
and return home at any time.
That's all?
That's all.
One hundred taels of silver, please.
Why is it so expensive?
Your young master is worth this price.
Or
you can be mine.
Ah.
No wonder someone told me not to come here.
I didn't expect you like this type.
But you're here.
He is strong
and diligent.
What's wrong with him?
He...
I have to take him away today.
I don't have enough money with me.
How about I give you 50 taels of silver first?
Is that okay?
Yicheng,
give her the money.
You're back.
Meng Feifei,
how dare you run a black shop?
I can't take Chief Su's words.
Guo Yongshi didn't deliver what he promised.
He's a complete rascal.
I suspect you're in cahoots with him.
25 years old, unmarried, martial arts skills, literate,
and capable of having five sons, right?
Which of these does Guo Yongshi not meet?
Moreover, I didn't even charge you.
How can you call this a scam?
Chief Su, you've been searching for a husband for a long time,
but you don't know what you want.
Now at least you know what you don't want.
If you're willing to give it a try,
you need to pay me 50 taels.
How dare you ask for money?
If it doesn't work,
you can smash my Matchmaker Pavilion.
You said that?
Yes, Master.
Boss.
Ah.
The future head of our escort agency
who fought with others in the street is back.
You're a girl.
You're like a ruffian all day.
Who will
let their son marry into our family?
Don't worry about my business.
Shopkeeper Li of Huayue Tower just said
you owed 80 taels of silver for wine this month.
You insisted on taking short-distance escort.
You're forgetful and perfunctory.
You lose more money than you make.
Who can't get married
and ruined the agency's reputation?
It's you.
Su Yuejiao,
even if you can't get married,
I can run the agency.
It's not your turn.
Nonsense.
Why not?
The agency was founded by my mother.
My sister was born before me.
I accept it.
But why can you inherit the Escort Agency?
Just because you're a woman?
If you're so capable, beat me.
And stop talking nonsense.
And I'm telling you,
from now on,
don't expect me to clean up your mess for you.
Don't even dream about it.
Dad, look at her.
Oh my.
Grandfather,
I suddenly feel uncomfortable in my heart.
Oh, Jiaojiao,
quick, help me back to the room.
I can't make it, oh no.
The Escort Agency will be mine sooner or later.
Humph.
Slow down.
Grandpa, are you okay now?
Am I not okay?
You're pretending to be sick again.
Always protecting him.
Oh, Zhen.
You started this escort agency.
Yu'er made it thrive.
Then I lost him.
It was devastating.
Jiaojiao had to run it at a young age.
Grandpa, I am Jiaojiao.
It's not necessary.
I've been running it for 18 years.
I'm just 18 years old.
At the age of marriage.
She doesn't want to get married?
It's not that I don't want to.
It's...
Alright, you can go now.
I'm going to sleep.
It's easy to get sleepy when it gets dark.
Master.
I'm so mad.
You finally come back.
Why don't you just stay in Yunjing?
Run out of money?
Or get into trouble?
They've come back safely.
And have knelt for hours.
Let them get up first.
What did he do in Yunjing?
Don't look at him.
Let him speak.
Master.
He went to Yunjing
to study in the academy.
Study?
Yes.
What do you want to study?
With your ability?
I know I'm not cut out for martial arts.
I want to study for the scholarly honor.
I've got a bad record in Ning'an.
I'm afraid I can't stay there.
So I want to go to the academy in Yunjing.
Yes.
He bought a lot of things for study.
You've been idling around,
and now you want to take the exam?
As long as I'm alive,
the Cheng family will only produce warriors.
You're not allowed to take the exam.
Yes.
I had a lot of feelings in Yunjing.
So I came back to tell you.
Really? Tell me,
what feelings do you have?
I want to get married.
Stand up.
Are you serious?
A man should start a family first.
For years,
I've been waiting for this day.
Finally, it's here.
My dear,
don't listen to his nonsense.
Who would want to marry him?
It's the daughter of the Yan family.
I fell in love with her at first sight.
The wedding date is set,
ten days later.
Look,
here's Miss Yan's betrothal card.
Fine,
just give me 50 taels of silver.
Miss,
add 200 taels of silver
to the betrothal gifts.
Once you board the escort cart,
the gifts will be delivered to your home.
That's good.
I'll be waiting for you.
Honey,
don't let that brat fool you again.
Nonsense.
Look, the betrothal card has been changed.
You said yourself,
who in Ning'an would marry him?
If we miss this chance,
when will we ever have a grandson?
And
Qi'er
is not suitable for martial arts.
But he has a chance to get married.
For your slight progress this time,
you can leave now.
And get ready to marry Miss Yan.
Yes.
Yicheng,
pack your luggage.
We'll go to Yunjing.
Okay.
Let's go.
Mom
What should I do?
A Jiao
Get up and practice.
If you don't get up,
the day will break.
Get up.
Come on.
Mom, I've learned this set of knife techniques.
You are so smart.
When you master it,
I'll teach you a new one.
How's it going?
Mom, you got hurt again.
It's nothing.
Jiao, remember,
in our Su's Escort Agency,
we live with the escort.
This little injury is nothing.
Alright, don't just stand there.
Go inside.
Go.
Mom,
Jiao escorted goods with me today.
Grandma,
I want to be an escort as good as you.